So visual assessment is really simple.
所以目测评估真的很简单
It's just looking at your dataset in its entirety in whatever program you like to use.
只需要查看你想要使用的程序中的整个数据集
For example, in Pandas here.
例如这里的 Pandas
So we've already gathered the data here.
我们已经将数据收集在这里
We've imported the Pandas library and read the CSV files into
导入 Pandas 库内 并将 CSV 文件读入这些 DataFrame
these data frames: patients, treatments, adverse reactions.
患者、治疗和不良反应
And now we can visually assess.
现在我们可以进行目测评估
We can just look through each table.
只需要浏览每一张表格
But because Pandas collapses rows here and scrolling in a Jupyter Notebook
但是因为 Pandas 折叠了一些行
is finicky as I'm frustratingly displaying here,
并且 Jupyter Notebook 中滚动浏览非常不方便
I tend to prefer to open files in a spreadsheet application like Google sheets or Excel.
我更倾向于在电子表格应用程序 (如 Google Sheets 或 Excel) 中打开文件
Here's Google sheets. Patients.CSV, treatments.CSV and adverse_reactions.CSV.
这是 Google Sheets patient.csv treatment.csv 和 adverse_reactions.csv
But some datasets are so large that,
但是有些数据集太大
spreadsheet programs crash when trying to open them,
打开它们时电子表格程序会崩溃
so your hand is forced into using something like Pandas sometimes.
因此有时迫不得已需要使用 Pandas 这样的工具
And again, we can just scroll through here and look for stuff.
同样地 我们可以滚动浏览 查找需要的东西
We can look for both quality and tidiness issues.
查看数据质量和整洁度问题
So you could start by looking for things like number of columns,
首先可以先查找列数
what the column headers are,
列标题
how many rows there are,
行数
what each row represents,
每一行表达的内容
what other types of values in the cells,
单元格中其他类型的值
like data types, integers,
如数据类型、整数
strings, floating point, et cetera.
字符串、浮点数等
But that isn't that efficient in visual assessment.
但是通过目测评估来查看这些内容的效率并不高
That's best done using programmatic assessment.
因此最好通过编程评估来完成
So what is visual assessment good for?
那么目测评估的优势在哪里呢？
Visual assessment is great for getting acquainted with
目测评估能够使你熟悉数据集
the dataset and just trying to understand what it's all about,
了解数据内容
like acquiring a mental picture of it.
就像将其映入你的脑海一样
Also, a lot of the time assessing is driven by the problem you want to solve,
此外很多时候之所以要评估数据 是因为你需要解决某些问题
like checking the values in the columns and rows you plan on using in your analysis.
比如查看各行各列的值以用于分析
Like hba1c_change for example.
如 hba1c_change 列
This can be effective in both visual assessment and programmatic.
目测评估和编程评估都可以有效地做到这一点
Non-directed visual assessment can be useful too.
非定向的目测评估也是有用的
Just scrolling aimlessly and stumbling upon issues,
可以随意滚动来发现一些问题
then dialing in on something once you have more of a clue of what issue you've spotted.
一旦对于这些问题有了更多的线索 即可进一步深入这些问题
At that point you can use more pinpointed assessments whether visual or programmatic.
通过目测或编程进行更精确的评估
So let's go back to the first thing that visual assessment was good for,
现在让我们回过头来看看目测评估的优势
getting acquainted with the meaning of the dataset.
即让你熟悉数据集的意义
So let's do that now. You'll look through the patients treatments and
接下来观察患者、治疗和不良反应表
adverse reactions table and really start to understand what each column represents.
真正了解每列的内容